hi joe my name is
student number 1901
from finn 324 think states in hong kong
and global banking section one group one
my own topic for short video is a
comparison of two similar insurance
plans between aia and prudential in hong
kong
and here is the content of my four parts
firstly look at the definition of this
type of insurance and its current
environment it is essentially a dual
type of insurance combining traditional
life insurance and investment features
its rate of return and risk will vary
depending on the portfolio and its value
at any given moment is determined
by the investment performance of its
funds at any time we can see from this
chart that the choice of numbers and
types of local investment linked life
insurance in hong kong is gradually
increasing
and also we can see the discharge the
number of products purchased in hong
kong is in an upward phase although its
total purchase value feels significantly
in 2017. it rebounded strongly in 2018
reflecting the fact that the actual
potential of this type of insurance
remains risk taken
our focus this time comes to the two
well-known insurance companies
let's take a look at the plans offered
by providential which offers three types
of the investment linked life insurance
policies all of them in the form of
whole life insurance plans
one of which requires regular premium
payments and is dominated in u.s dollars
which is not too expensive
while the other two have
now some premium and two have completely
different minimum investment amounts one
with a minimum of twenty thousand us
dollars and the other with a minimum of
one million hong kong dollars
although all three have a debt benefit
of 105 of the policy amount value
now let's look at the plans launched by
aia which has 94 in total one more than
potential in these four planes the debt
benefit is still 105 percent of the
policy of accounts value but only one
policy plan is a whole life plan other
two of the other three covers
periods can reach the policy holder's
age of 80 and one at the age 100.
in this plan two are for regular
premiums and the remaining two are for
non-sum premiums with a minimum
investment of 100 500 000 hong kong
dollars for one and a u.s dollar of
fifteen thousand for other nam sound
premiums the other two regular premiums
one with the fixed and modest premium
payments and other with a different sum
insurance depending on the policy's age
gender and other factors
my understanding of how to choose from
the plans of these two companies is that
for people who are considering more
choice and flexibility and have a
limited income level they can go for
plans over by aia although owning one
thing is for whole life awareness for
those with a higher income level and who
are more committed to a fixed and
lifetime plans potential would be a
better option for them however overall i
would hope that people will look at the
long term and need to first consider how
they can grow the value of their assets
over the downturn and stately
rather than pursuing short-term returns
if you want to get a right return on
your investment having a long-term
investment plans of the life insurance
is the best way to go and this is the
basis for choosing the right investment
linked life insurance policy
from this point of view prudential is
better relatively
that's all of my presentation thanks for
watching